<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Lord Sudo</title>
    <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Lord Sudo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Progress Log - Week 1</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/progress_log_week1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/progress_log_week1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Week starting:&lt;/strong&gt; 12th Jan 2026&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This week marked my return from a much-needed break spent doing the highly advanced technique known as &lt;em&gt;touching grass&lt;/em&gt;. After a busy year, I came back feeling relaxed, refreshed, and in a surprisingly good mental state.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Instead of easing in gently, I decided to jump straight back in and see how rusty I’d become.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Took me a whole 2 hours to remember the master password to my password manager before I could log in anywhere. Never change your password before a long break. I didnt even remember why I changed it in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Mayhem: My PerfectRoot CTF 2025 Recap</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/perfectrootctf2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/perfectrootctf2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-lights-camera-chaos&#34;&gt;🎉 Lights, Camera, Chaos!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you heard loud keyboard smashing on the weekend of December 5th…&lt;br&gt;&#xA;yeah, that was probably us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PerfectRoot CTF 2025 went live, thousands of players stormed the gates, the Discord server transformed into a marketplace of panic and memes, and somewhere in the background I was praying the infra wouldn’t spontaneously combust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spoiler: it didn’t.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Miracles &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;perfectroot-ctf-2025--my-behind-the-scenes-recap-organized-chaos-done-right&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PerfectRoot CTF 2025 — My Behind-the-Scenes Recap (Organized Chaos Done Right)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PerfectRoot CTF 2025 is officially in the books — and wow, what a ride.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This year’s event wasn’t just bigger… it was louder, faster, and way more chaotic in the best possible way. If last year was a warm-up jog, this year was a sprint uphill while juggling flaming Docker containers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Marked by Dust - ADHoc Intel Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/markedbydust/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/markedbydust/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-marked-by-dust&#34;&gt;🕯️ Marked by Dust&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Category:&lt;/strong&gt; OSINT&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Time has buried many secrets, but even in the dust, a precise place remains.”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Question says:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Every place has its special words; find the ones that belong to this artifact&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;prologue--the-forgotten-door&#34;&gt;Prologue — The Forgotten Door&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;It began with silence.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;No coordinates, no hints — only an image.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;A sun-scorched door of ancient wood, framed in cracked earth, its texture heavy with history. It stared back at the solver like a memory half-recalled, daring them to look closer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dig Deeper Walkthrough - Dewald Roode Cybersecurity Hackathon 2025</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/digdeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/digdeeper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-prologue-whispers-beneath-the-noise&#34;&gt;🕳️ Prologue: Whispers Beneath the Noise&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the endless expanse of the cyber realm, secrets rarely scream — they whisper. Steganography is the ancient art of these whispers: the delicate craft of hiding a truth so deeply that even when it is in plain sight, it remains unseen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where cryptography cloaks a message behind an unbreakable cipher, steganography conceals its very existence. A song that carries a confession in static. An image that smiles innocently while concealing a weapon beneath its pixels. A file that hums one story to the ear while hiding another for those patient enough to listen closer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3=crowd? - Bitwall CTF OSINT Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/3crowdwalkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/3crowdwalkthrough/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-3crowd&#34;&gt;🕳️ 3=crowd?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A journey into nothingness.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-prologue&#34;&gt;🕯️ Prologue&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The screen flickered. No IP addresses to scan. No EXIF tags to scrub. No usernames to pivot from. Only a prompt:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“All through time, we have strived to achieve precision in all our workings.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Come our beloved cyberspace, and nothing became one of the most important fundamentals of the entire industry.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Trace back its true origin and describe in &lt;strong&gt;three words&lt;/strong&gt; that which is known to all yet unknown to all.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CyberDefenders: 3CX Supply Chain Attack</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/3cxlab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/3cxlab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;prologue-the-quiet-before-the-storm&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prologue: The Quiet Before the Storm&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the quietest moments of routine operations, danger often stirs. A trusted software update, something so mundane, becomes the entry point for a dark and malicious force. The &lt;strong&gt;3CX Supply Chain Attack&lt;/strong&gt;—an incident where trust was manipulated, and a seemingly harmless software update became a weapon of digital warfare. Prepare yourself, for the tale is one of hidden danger, covert movements, and the eerie calm before a storm. Let’s walk through this, step by step, through the veil of deceit and into the truth that lies beneath.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
