<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CTF on Lord Sudo</title>
    <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/tags/ctf/</link>
    <description>Recent content in CTF on Lord Sudo</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://lordsudo.github.io/tags/ctf/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Mayhem: My PerfectRoot CTF 2025 Recap</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/perfectrootctf2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/perfectrootctf2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-lights-camera-chaos&#34;&gt;🎉 Lights, Camera, Chaos!&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If you heard loud keyboard smashing on the weekend of December 5th…&lt;br&gt;&#xA;yeah, that was probably us.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PerfectRoot CTF 2025 went live, thousands of players stormed the gates, the Discord server transformed into a marketplace of panic and memes, and somewhere in the background I was praying the infra wouldn’t spontaneously combust.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spoiler: it didn’t.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Miracles &lt;em&gt;do&lt;/em&gt; happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;perfectroot-ctf-2025--my-behind-the-scenes-recap-organized-chaos-done-right&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PerfectRoot CTF 2025 — My Behind-the-Scenes Recap (Organized Chaos Done Right)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;PerfectRoot CTF 2025 is officially in the books — and wow, what a ride.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This year’s event wasn’t just bigger… it was louder, faster, and way more chaotic in the best possible way. If last year was a warm-up jog, this year was a sprint uphill while juggling flaming Docker containers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dig Deeper Walkthrough - Dewald Roode Cybersecurity Hackathon 2025</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/digdeeper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/digdeeper/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-prologue-whispers-beneath-the-noise&#34;&gt;🕳️ Prologue: Whispers Beneath the Noise&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the endless expanse of the cyber realm, secrets rarely scream — they whisper. Steganography is the ancient art of these whispers: the delicate craft of hiding a truth so deeply that even when it is in plain sight, it remains unseen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Where cryptography cloaks a message behind an unbreakable cipher, steganography conceals its very existence. A song that carries a confession in static. An image that smiles innocently while concealing a weapon beneath its pixels. A file that hums one story to the ear while hiding another for those patient enough to listen closer.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3=crowd? - Bitwall CTF OSINT Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/3crowdwalkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://lordsudo.github.io/posts/3crowdwalkthrough/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;-3crowd&#34;&gt;🕳️ 3=crowd?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;A journey into nothingness.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;-prologue&#34;&gt;🕯️ Prologue&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The screen flickered. No IP addresses to scan. No EXIF tags to scrub. No usernames to pivot from. Only a prompt:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“All through time, we have strived to achieve precision in all our workings.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Come our beloved cyberspace, and nothing became one of the most important fundamentals of the entire industry.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Trace back its true origin and describe in &lt;strong&gt;three words&lt;/strong&gt; that which is known to all yet unknown to all.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
